

## victor smart

WEB DEVELOPER

• 12 crest St, abeokuta, ogun state.

victchubxy@gmail.com

https://vic-prof.herokuapp.com/

#### **PROFILE**

A passionate web developer with flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time. passionate about building world class web development projects.

I design and develop userfriendly websites such as Elearning platform, Eecommerce website, voting platform, instant messaging web app, chatbots, blogs, portfolio etc.

I help businesses with conversion-led website, that guarantee high profile page view user experience and improve sale through automations.

### **SKILLS**

Python/Django/Bootstrap

•••••

Html/Css/ReactJS/Javascript

Nodejs/sQI/NosQI/MysQI

creativity

•••••

teamwork

problem solving

#### .....

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# INSTRUCTOR AND DEVELOPER Nov 2023 - Present 720 degree hub

- work with a great team and cultivate excellent relationship with client, conduct competitive analysis, design and develop application system to completion.
- Establish quality instructor-student relationship and facilitate a dynamic and engaging learning environment that equips student with knowledge and skills needed to succeed in the field of IT.
- ability to oversee and supervise a highly robust project to completion.
- · develop quality leadership skills

# WEB DEVELOPER INTERN may 2021 - Sep 2022 HNG Inc

- i collaborated with great team to conduct competitive analysis and organize, design, document, application systems (from scratch).
- create new features, effectively fix bugs and optimize the overall performance of the application.
- Automate business process with API-driven workflow tools like Zapier
- work with a great team and cultivate excellent relationship with client that lead to a strong base of referral businesses.

### WEB DEVELOPER INTERN apr 2020 - jun 2021

### NXTECH

- establish an interactive and dynamic website that guarantee high profile page view user experience.
- design, develop and document a SaaS product with vendor management dashboard, product tracking, reporting tools, product categorization, mobile support etc. with Django and React.js.
- responsible for fullstack web development for all cleint projects.
- enhance the application features to effectively fix bugs and optimize the overall performance.
- help the company make better decision when building and improving app functionality by conducting user interviews
- increase customer satisfaction by 35% and customer retention by 30%.

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Bachelor's Degree in Physics

mar 2014 - aug 2018

## university of nigeria nsukka

- University of Nigeria Nsukka, Bachelor's degree (university degree) in Education Physics/Education